{
    "id": "0040092ad8114d7ab503d1003587a242",
    "title": "Adverbs grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d1e49320b2f44671a432a479a7e4a42a",
            "title": "Adverbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She has done everything – she has …………………… been a soldier.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "even",
                        "often",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Although I lived with her for ten years, I could …………………… understand her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have …………………… finished painting the house.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "always",
                        "almost",
                        "even"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is my teacher, but she is ………………… my friend.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "also",
                        "even",
                        "just"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. he could do a thing like that.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Only",
                        "Just",
                        "Also"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… look in the mirror before starting to drive.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Ever",
                        "Always",
                        "Often"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We are ……………………… going for two days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "only",
                        "often"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Some of us want a new system …………………, not everybody agrees.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "however",
                        "and",
                        "then"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I worked until five o’clock. …………………… I went home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Then",
                        "Still",
                        "After"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He always wears a coat, …………………. in summer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "even",
                        "also",
                        "often"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}